propertyshowrooms.com 2014-06-30

# Propertyshowrooms.com Privacy Statement

Global Prospects S.L operating Propertyshowrooms.com and IPIN is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Accordingly, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and will continue to review and improve our privacy policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of consumer information.

Global Prospects SL adheres to the confidentiality of each and every client and guarantees the privacy of all databases and customer lists. The databases remain the property of each customer and will not be given or shared with any other company or individual. Security systems have been put in place to expel any likelihood of unauthorised access to the customer's database and confidential list information.

Please read the full privacy policy below.

## Contacting you

By registering your contact details on Propertyshowrooms.com including registration as a member of the IPIN Global (IPIN) you agree that we can contact you at anytime via any method using the details submitted to us, you grant us the right to contact you until you notify us not to.

## Email Marketing

By registering your contact details on Propertyshowrooms.com including registration as a member of the IPIN Global (IPIN) you agree that we can send you marketing emails at any time, these will continue until you notify us to remove you from our mailing list.

## Anti-Spam

Global Prospects SL Limited adheres to the principles of permission marketing and does not knowingly send out messages to databases where customers have not willingly agreed to receive those messages. This policy has been put in place to protect the user from unsolicited email. If you would like to unsubscribe from our mailing list then please [click here](http://www.propertyshowrooms.com/unsubscribe.asp "Unsubscribe").

## Standard Information:

Found in every communication sent over the Internet. Using this standard information, we can infer the following information: browser type (e.g. Netscape or Internet Explorer); operating system (e.g. Macintosh or Windows); browser language (e.g. Java or Unix); Internet service provider (e.g. FreeServe or AOL).

## Personal Information

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information. For instance, you may provide your address or email address in order to receive further information or create an account. We may collect this information and use this information to respond to your request for the information requested. In order to service your requirements we have to share your contact details with our panel of vetted real estate agents in order for them to contact you and help you find a suitable property. Every one of our vetted agents has agreed to our operating terms and conditions which explicitly states that under no circumstances can they share any of your personal details with any external agents or third parties.

www.propertyshowrooms.com will not share your details with any external agents, third parties who have not been pre-vetted by ourselves.

For more information on the types of personally identifiable information collected by us, please email us at legal@propertyshowrooms.com

## Cookies and Opt-Out:

Like most Internet sites, we may use "cookies" to enhance user's experience on the Web. We cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies in no way damage your system or files.

We use information from our Web site log files to understand how visitors use our site and to recommend future site improvements. No personally identifiable information is used in these analyses. User information collected via the site is date, time, and IP address.

## Links:

This privacy statement applies solely to the technology and Web site Propertyshowrooms.com. Our Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Consumer Privacy:

If you should have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact legal@propertyshowrooms.com. We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Statement, as we may update it from time to time.

## E Commerce (EC Directive) Regulations 2002

The following information is required by the Electronic Commerce (EC Directive) Regulations 2002.

Service Provided by www.propertyshowrooms.com which is an operational business unit of Global Prospects S.L.

Global Prospects SL  
Edif River Playa 2, Calle Santa Barbara 1  
Fuengirola/Malaga   
Spain, 29640
